A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Karen Davis papers, SG 2 FA1127
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 1971-2009; 2; 15.76 Cubic Feet 41 letter document box and 1 half-box
  - 123 - "Toward Universal Access," AARP, 1990 March 12 (Box 27, Folder 211)
  - 124 - "Health, Health Insurance, and Older Adults", 1990 August (Box 27, Folder 212)
  - 125 - "Health Insurance and Access to Health Care," Research in Human Capital and Development, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 213)
  - 126 - "Providing Universal and Affordable Health Care: Learning from Experience," Improving Access to Affordable Health Care, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 214)
  - 127 - "Affordable Health: Future Directions for the Federal Government", 1990 September 23 (Box 27, Folder 215)
  - 128 - "Health Care: Problems and Prospects for America's Families", 1990 October 12 (Box 27, Folder 216)
  - 129 - "Paying for Preventive Services," APHA Meeting, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 214-218)
  - 130 - "The Health Care Cost in Crisis: The Case of Physician Services", 1990 October 4 (Box 28, Folder 219)
  - 131 - "An Aging Population: Health Policy Issues", 1990 October 11 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - 132 - "Expanding Medicare and Employer Plans to Achieve Universal Health Insurance," Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA), 1991 May 15 (Box 28, Folder 221-222)
  - 133 - 'Impact of Physician Payment Reform", 1990 November 2 (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - 134 - "A National Health Plan for the U.S.: Time for Action," HealthWeek, 1990 November (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - 135 - "Equity and Health Care Policy: The American Experience," Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Conference, 1990 November 12-16 (Box 29, Folder 225)
  - 136 - "Reform of the Health Care System: Issues for the 1990s", 1990 November 29 (Box 29, Folder 226)
  - 137 - "The Skyrocketing Cost of Health Care", 1990 December 7 (Box 29, Folder 227)
  - 138 - "Public Financing of Health Care: Implications for AIDS and HIV-Positive Individuals," National Commission on AIDS, 1990 December 18 (Box 29, Folder 228)
  - 140 - "The "New" Health Care System: Views on Reform the Consumer View," American Hospital Association, 1991 March 6 (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - 143 - "Physician Payment Review: Implications for Business and the Private Sector," Health Advisory Council, 1991 April 3 (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - 144 - "Financing Health Care for Persons with HIV Infection and AIDS: Policy Options," National Commission on AIDS, 1991 April (Box 29, Folder 231)
  - 145 - "Health Policy Issues on the National Agenda", 1991 May 8 (Box 29, Folder 232)
  - 146 - "Choice of Medicare or Private Health Insurance: An Approach to Universal Health Insurance Coverage", 1991 May 8 (Box 30, Folder 233)
  - 147 - "NHI: Government Activity", 1991 May 17 (Box 30, Folder 234)
  - 148 - "Expanding Medicaid to Cover Uninsured Americans," Health Affairs Letter to Editor, 1991 April 30 (Box 30, Folder 235)
  - 149 - "Laying the Groundwork," AARP Conference, 1991 June 10 (Box 30, Folder 236)
  - 150 - "Financing Medical Care for the Most Vulnerable -- The Uninsured, the Unemployed and the Homeless", 1991 June 12 (Box 30, Folder 237)
  - 151 - "Revenue Sources of Health Care Delivery Systems", 1991 June 17 (Box 30, Folder 238)
  - 152 - "Inequality and Access to Health Care," The Milbank Quarterly, 1991 Novebmer (Box 30, Folder 239)
    - "Inequality and Access to Health Care", 1991 November; 2013:002:002
  - 153 - "Medicaid Payments and Utilization of Medical Services by the Poor", 1976 (Box 30, Folder 240)
  - 154 - "Choice of Public or Private Health Insurance: An Approach to Universal Health Insurance Coverage with All Payer Cost Controls", 1991 September-December (Box 30, Folder 241)
  - 155 - "Life Satisfaction and Older Adults", 1991 September (Box 30, Folder 242)
  - 156 - "Equity and Health Care Policy", 1991 September (Box 31, Folder 243)
  - 157 - "Caring for Aging Women," Taking Care: The Changing Roles of Women in Health Care, 1991 September (Box 31, Folder 244)
  - 158 -"Public Benefits Outreach: Major Lessons", 1991 September 12-13 (Box 31, Folder 245)
  - 159 - "Medicare as the Basis for All Payer Provider Payment Reform", 1991 October 3-4 (Box 31, Folder 246)
  - 160 - "The Impact of Medicare and Medicaid on Access to Medical Care," reprint, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 247)
  - 161 - "Controlling Health Care Costs", 1991 October 28 (Box 31, Folder 248)
  - 162 - "Closing the Gap in Health Insurance Coverage for African Americans", 1991 October 31-November 2 (Box 31, Folder 249)
  - 163 - "Health Care Costs and Reimbursement Issues" and "Health Insurance and Long Term Care," American Physical Therapy Association, 1991 November 2 (Box 31, Folder 250)
  - 164 - "Principles for Reform," Commonwealth Fund Commission on Elderly People Living Alone, 1991 November 6 (Box 31, Folder 251)
  - 165 - "Medicare Provider Payment Reform: Implications for the U.S. Health System", 1991 November 17 (Box 31, Folder 252)
  - 166 - "International Approaches to Health Care Financing," Chile Ministry of Health, 1991 December 4 (Box 31, Folder 253)
  - 167 - "Health Care Reform and Preventive Services," Report to the Center of Disease Control, 1992 August 21 (Box 31, Folder 254)
  - 168 - "The U.S. Health System: Major Problems and Options for Reform," Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD), 1992 February (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - OECD, 1992 February 10; 2013:002:003
  - 169 - "The Changing Nature of Employee Health Benefits", 1992 May (Box 32, Folder 256)
  - 170 - "Health Financing Reform: Implications for the Health Care Industry", 1992 February 17 (Box 32, Folder 257)
  - 171 - "Health Care Reform: Democratic Alternatives," Democratic National Committee, 1992 April 2-5 (Box 32, Folder 258)
  - 172 - "Financing Health Care", 1991 July 17 (Box 32, Folder 259)
  - 173 - "Single Payer Approach to Health Care Reform," Governor's National Leadership Conference, 1992 January 10-11 (Box 32, Folder 260)
  - 174 - "An Overview of Health Care Reform," The Mildred and Claude Pepper Foundation and The Fraternal Order of the Eagles, 1992 May 18-19 (Box 32, Folder 261)
  - 175 - "An Overview of Health Care Reform," Bristol-Myers Squibb Corporate Advisory Council Meeting, 1992 May 28-30 (Box 32, Folder 262)
  - 176 - "Early Returns on RBRVS," Comptroller General's Health Advisory Committee Meeting, 1992 June 4-5 (Box 32, Folder 263)
  - 177 - "An Overview of Health Care Reform," Association of Bioscience Financial Office (ABFO), 1992 June 9-12 (Box 33, Folder 264)
  - 178 - "An Overview of Health Care Reform," Macy Foundation Conference, 1992 June 11-12 (Box 33, Folder 265)
  - 179 - Johns Hopkins School of Public Health 75th Anniversary Symposium, 1991 October-November (Box 33, Folder 266)
  - 179A - Johns Hopkins School of Public Health 75th Anniversary Symposium, 1991 October-November (Box 33, Folder 267)
  - 180 - "Medicaid and the Working Poor," Health Affairs, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 268)
  - 185 - "Medicare as the Basis for All-Payer Provider Payment Reform," AFI American Health Policy, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - 186 - "A Comprehensive Overview of Health Care Reform," Senate Staff Presentation, 1992 June 8 (Box 33, Folder 270)
  - 187 - Travelers National Health Care Quality Conference, 1992 June 15-16 (Box 33, Folder 271)
  - 188 - "Health Care Reform," Executive Nurse Fellowship Program Retreat, 1992 August 14-17 (Box 33, Folder 272)
  - 190 - "An Overview of Health Care Reform," Long Island Conference on Health Care, 1992 September 18 (Box 33, Folder 273)
  - 191 - United Nations Conference on Aging, 1992 September 30-October 2 (Box 33, Folder 274)
  - 192 - "Health Care Reform and New Decisions for Business," Forbes Magazine, 1992 October 1-2 (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - 193 - "National Health Care Reform and Preventive Services: Implications for Employers," Johns Hopkins Public Health Conference, 1992 December 8 (Box 34, Folder 276)
  - 194 - "The Economy and Health Care Reform", 1992 December 14 (Box 34, Folder 277)
  - 195 - "Health Care Reform: Problems and Options," Health Care Outlook, 1993 January 21 (Box 34, Folder 278)
  - 196 - "Health Care Reform in the Clinton Administration: What Does it Mean?," National Media Conference, Columbia University, 1993 February 8 (Box 34, Folder 279-280)
  - 197 - "Health Care Reform: Problems, Issues, and Options," Grantmakers in Health National Meeting on Health Philanthropy, 1993 February 19 (Box 35, Folder 281)
  - 198 - "Physician Payment Reform," New York University, 1993 March 4 (Box 35, Folder 282)
  - 199 - "Health Care Reform in the U.S.: The Contribution of Health Services Research to the Debate," New York Academy of Science, 1993 March 25 (Box 35, Folder 283)
  - 200 - "Health Care Reform: Issues and Options," Hermann Biggs Society, 1993 April 8 (Box 35, Folder 284)
  - 201 - "Medicaid State Budget Pac Man," Graduate School of Management and Urban Policy, 1993 April 19 (Box 35, Folder 285)
  - 202 - "The Mission Half: Improved Health Care for Women," Council on Foundations, 1993 April 26 (Box 35, Folder 286)
  - 203 - "Women's Health: Myths and Realities," Jefferson Medical College, 1993 May 7 (Box 35, Folder 287)
  - 204 - "Health Care Cost Containment: Issues and Options," Columbia University Health Policy Forum, 1993 May 11 (Box 35, Folder 288)
  - 205 - "Health Care Perspectives," Maine Health Care Conference, 1993 May 14 (Box 36, Folder 289)
  - 206 - "Women's Health: Myths and Realities," Cornell Medical College, 1993 May 26 (Box 36, Folder 290)
  - 207 - "Building A Competitive Workforce for the 1990s: Is Corporate America Keeping Pace with Change?", 1993 May (Box 36, Folder 291)
  - 208 - National Health System Reform: Proposals and Expectations in Perspective," Columbia University, 1993 June 8 (Box 36, Folder 292)
  - 209 - "National Health Care Reform: Window of Opportunity," Women in Health Management, Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1993 June 8 (Box 36, Folder 293)
  - 210 - "The Importance of Choice in Medicaid Home Care Programs: Maryland, Michigan, and Texas," Press Conference, 1993 June 9 (Box 36, Folder 294)
  - 211 - Association of Health Services Research (AHSR) Annual Meeting, 1993 June 27 (Box 36, Folder 295)
  - 212 - "Meet the Experts Workshop," Association for Health and Research (AHSR), 1993 June 9 (Box 36, Folder 296)
  - 213 - "Survey of Women's Health", 1993 July 14 (Box 36, Folder 297)
  - 214 - "Health Care Reform: Implications for Urban Health," National Public Health and Hospital Institute, 1993 August 6 (Box 37, Folder 298)
  - 215 - "Health Care Reform in the United States: Issues and Prospects," Harkness Fellows Orientation Program, 1993 August 25 (Box 37, Folder 299)
  - 216 - "The Commonwealth Fund Program Activities," Harkness Fellows Orientation Program, 1993 August 25 (Box 37, Folder 300)
  - 217 - "Reflections of Health care Reform: Where Do We Go From Here?," Department of Geriatrics and Adult Development, 1993 September 1 (Box 37, Folder 301)
  - 218 - "Myths and Realities about the Health of American Women," American Medical Writers Association, Yale Club, 1993 September 14 (Box 37, Folder 302)
  - 219 - "Myths and Realities about the Health of American Women," World Economic Development Conference, 1993 September 25 (Box 37, Folder 303)
  - 220 - "Health Care Costs for Older Workers," Fund Survey Press Release, 1993 September 29 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - 221 - "Myths and Realities about the Health of American Women with A Focus on the Elderly and Underprivileged," Franciscan Heritage Seminar, 1993 October 1 (Box 37, Folder 305)
  - 222 - "Managed Competition from the Patient's Perspective," Health Services Improvement Fund, 1993 October 20 (Box 37, Folder 306)
  - 223 - Campaign for Women's Health, a Project of the Older Women's League, Commonwealth Fund, 1993 November 10 (Box 37, Folder 307)
  - 224 - Health Insurance Survey, Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, 1993 November 10 (Box 37, Folder 308)
  - 225 - "President Clinton's Health Care Plan: Issues of Access, Costs, and Quality," IMCARE's Institute on Quality and Accountability, 1993 November 13 (Box 37, Folder 309)
  - 226 - "President Clinton's Health Care Reform Plan: How It Will Effect the Practice of Medicine in the U.S.," New York Academy of Medicine, 1993 November 15 (Box 37, Folder 310)
  - 227 - "The Americans Over 55 at Work Program: Policy Recommendations for the 21st Century," GSA Anual Scientific Meeting, 1993 November 22 (Box 37, Folder 311)
  - 228 - "Aging and Active: Dimensions of Productive Engagement Among Older Americans," GSA Annual Scientific Meeting, 1993 November 23 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - 229 - "Women's Health: Myths and Stereotypes," harkness Health Conference, 1993 December 8-9 (Box 38, Folder 313)
  - 230 - "Universal Coverage: Build on Medicare and Employers," Health Affairs, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 314)
  - 231 - "Managed Care: Promise and Concerns," Health Affairs, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - 232 - "Where Are We, How Did We Get Here, Where Are We Going?", 1995 January (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - 233 - "Choice Matters", 1995 (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - 234 - "Health Insurance: The Size and Shape of the Problem", 1995 (Box 38, Folder 318)
  - 235 - "The Federal Budget and Women's Health," American Journal of Public Health, 1995 August (Box 38, Folder 319)
  - 236 - "Managing Care in the Public Interest", undated (Box 38, Folder 320)
  - 237 - "Medicare Analysis: Preserving and Strengthening Medicare," Health Affairs, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 321)
  - 238 - "Importance of Preserving Medicare," Health Law News, 1996 April (Box 38, Folder 322)
  - 239 - "Philanthropy and the Medically Homeless," The Chronicle of Philanthropy, 1996 July 25 (Box 38, Folder 323)
  - 240 - "Rules Needed to Ensure Efficiency and Quality In Medicare Managed Care," The Internist, 1996 July-August (Box 38, Folder 324)
  - 242 - "The Growth of Managed Care: Implications for Patients," New York academy of Medicine, 1996 January 16 (Box 38, Folder 325)
  - 243 - "Incremental Coverage of the Uninsured," Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA), 1996 September 11 (Box 39, Folder 326)
  - 244 - "Uninsured in an Era of Managed Care", AHSR Presidential Address, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 327)
  - 245 - "Insurance Matters for Low-Income Adults: Results from a Five-State Survey," Health Affairs, 1997 September-October (Box 39, Folder 328)
  - 246 - "Changing Health Care Systems and Rheumatic Disease", 1996 (Box 39, Folder 329)
  - 247 - "Meeting the Health Needs of America's Children," Aspen Institute, 1997 February (Box 39, Folder 330)
  - 248 - "Economic Trends and Health of Low Income People", 1997 May 23 (Box 39, Folder 331)
  - 250 - "Equity and Health Policy", undated (Box 39, Folder 332)
  - 251 - "Incremental Health Insurance Coverage: Building on the Current System", undated (Box 39, Folder 333)
  - 252 - "Economics and Urban Health," New York Academy of Medicine, 1997 November (Box 39, Folder 334)
  - 253 - "Assuring Quality, Information, and Choice in Managed Care," Inquiry, 1997 October (Box 39, Folder 335)
  - 254 - "Assuring Safe Motherhood Before and After Women Become Mothers," World Health Organization 50th Anniversary Symposium, 1998 April 6 (Box 39, Folder 336)
  - 255 - "Improving Lives through Information," Health Affairs, 1999 March-April (Box 39, Folder 337)
  - 256 - "Shaping the Future of Medicare," Health Services Research, undated (Box 39, Folder 338)
  - 257 - "International Health Policy: Common Problems, Alternative Strategies," Health Affairs, 1999 May-June (Box 39, Folder 339)
  - 258 - "The Cost of Health System Change: Public Discontent in Five Nations," Health Affairs, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 340)
  - 259 - "Understanding Diverse Needs of the Medicare Population: Implications for Medicare Reform," Journal of Aging and Social Policy, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 341)
  - 260 - "Managed Care and Women's Health: An Overview", 1998 December 21 (Box 39, Folder 342)
  - 261 - "Managed Care Quality: Can the Market Work Without Government?" Journal of Health Politics, Policy, and the Law, 1999 April (Box 39, Folder 343)
  - 262 - "Regulating Managed Care: Theory Practice, and Future Options", 1999 (Box 39, Folder 344)
  - 263 - "Health Care for Low-Income People", undated (Box 39, Folder 345)
  - 264 - "The Danish Health System Through An American Lens", 1998 September 17 (Box 39, Folder 346)
  - 265 - "Investing in Health Services Research: The Commonwealth Fund's Experience", 1999 December-2000 January (Box 39, Folder 347)
  - 266 - "Health Insurance Market and Income Inequality: Findings from an International Health Policy Survey," Health Policy, 1999 December (Box 40, Folder 348)
  - 267 - "Care for the Elderly: How the World is Coping," Health Affairs, 2000 May-June (Box 40, Folder 349)
  - 268 - "Listening to Parents: A National Survey of Parents with Young Children," American Medical Association, 1998 March (Box 40, Folder 350)
  - 269 - "Women's Health and Managed Care", 2000 (Box 40, Folder 351)
  - 270 - "Baxter Allegiance Prize Acceptance", 2000 (Box 40, Folder 352)
  - 271 - "International Journal of Integrated Care: Significance of IJIC", 2000 October (Box 40, Folder 353)
  - 272 - "A 2020 Vision for American Health Care," American Medical Association, 2000 December (Box 40, Folder 354)
  - 273 - "Universal Coverage in the United States: Lessons from Experience of the 20th Century," Journal of Urban Health, 1999-2001 March (Box 40, Folder 355)
  - 274 - "Gaps in Health Coverage Among Working-Age Americans and the Consequences," Journal of Health Care for the Poor and Underserved, 2001 August (Box 40, Folder 356)
  - 275 - "The Danish Health System Through An American Lens," Health Policy, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 357)
  - 276 - "Preparing for the Future: A 2020 Vision for American Health Care," Academic Medicine, 2001 April (Box 40, Folder 358)
  - 277 - "Physicians' Views on Quality of Care: A Five-Country Comparison," Physician Survey, 2001 May-June (Box 40, Folder 359)
  - 278 - "Medicare Versus Private Insurance: Rhetoric and Reality," Health Affairs, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 360)
  - 280 - "Creating Consensus on Coverage Choices," Health Affairs, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 361)
  - 281 - Commentary on "The Costs and Consequences of begin Uninsured," Medical Care Research and Review, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 362)
  - 282 - "Obtaining Greater Value from Health Care: The Roles of the U.S. Government," Government and Health, 2003 November-December (Box 40, Folder 363)
  - 283 - Commentary "Half Full? Half Empty? A New Year's Assessment of U.S. Health Policy," Medscape, 2004 January (Box 40, Folder 364)
  - 284 - "U.S. Health Policy: Time for Action on the Uninsured," Health Policy, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 365)
  - 285 - "Consumer-Directed Health care: Will It Improve Health System Performance?", 2004 August (Box 40, Folder 366)
  - 286 - "Primary Care and Health System Performance: Adults' Experience in Five Countries," Health Affairs, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 367)
  - 287 - How to Control Healthcare Costs: Take A Walk on the Supply Side," Medscape, 2005 March 25 (Box 40, Folder 368)
  - 288 - "Shared Responsibility: U.S. Employers and the Provision of Health Insurance to Employees," Health Affairs, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 369)
  - 289 - "Visions of the Future," The Quality Solution: Stakeholder's Guide to Improving Healthcare, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 370)
  - 290 - "Toward A High Performance Health System: The Commonwealth Fund's New Commission," Grant Watch, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 371)
  - 291 - "Medicare Extra: A Comprehensive Benefit Option for Medicare Beneficiaries," Health Affairs, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 372-373)
  - 292 - "A 2020 Vision of Patient-Centered Primary Care," Journal of General Internal Medicine, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 374)
  - 293 - "A Supply-Side Approach to Health Care," Seattle Times, 2005 October 13 (Box 41, Folder 375)
  - 294 - "Taking the Pulse of Health Care Systems: Experiences of Patients with Health Problems in Six Countries," Health Affairs, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 376)
  - 295 - "Medicaid: A Vision for the Next 40 Years," Medscape, 2005 November 7 (Box 41, Folder 377)
  - 296 - "Patient-Centered Primary Care: It Can Happen Here," Medscape, 2005 December 9 (Box 41, Folder 378)
  - 297 - "Health Policy Year In Review: A Mixed Bag," Medscape, 2005 December 30 (Box 41, Folder 379)
  - 298 - "Medicare at 40," Health Care Financing Review, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 380-381)
  - 299 - "A High-Performance Health System: The Role of Patients", 2006 March 6 (Box 42, Folder 382)
  - 300 - "Adoption of Patient-Centered Care Practices by Physicians", 2006 April 10 (Box 42, Folder 383)
  - 301 - "Providing Health Insurance for All: What We Can Learn from Massachusetts," Medscape, 2006 May (Box 42, Folder 384)
  - 302 - "Aiming High: 10 Steps to a High-Performance Health System," Medscape, 2006 June 5 (Box 42, Folder 385)
  - 303 - "Commentary - Achieving a High-Performance Health System: High Reliability Organizations within a Broader Agenda," Health Research and Education Trust, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 386)
  - 304 - "Consumer-Directed Health Care: A Panacea or the Wrong Prescription," The Physician Executive, 2006 September-October (Box 42, Folder 387)
  - 306 - "The Time is Right for Healthcare Reform," Medscape, 2007 January 8 (Box 42, Folder 388)
  - 307 - "Access to Care: Key to a High-Performance Health System," Futurescan: Healthcare Trends and Implications 2007-2012 (Box 42, Folder 389)
  - 308 - "Uninsured in America", 2006 (Box 42, Folder 390)
  - 309 - "NEJM P4P Editorial", 2007 January 29 (Box 42, Folder 391)
  - 320 - "Measuring and Improving Health System Performance: What Can Healthcare Management Educators Do?" 2008 Pattullo Lecture, 2008-2009 (Box 42, Folder 392)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1971-1974 (Box 165, Folder 1248-1249)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1975-1981 (Box 166, Folder 1250-1252)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1981-1982 (Box 167, Folder 1253-1255)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1983-1985 (Box 168, Folder 1256-1258)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 1259-1261)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1984-1986 (Box 170, Folder 1262-1264)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 1265-1266)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 1267-1269)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1988-1992 (Box 173, Folder 1270-1274)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1988-1989 (Box 174, Folder 1275-1277)
  - Book Chapters, Books, Testimonies, 1988-1992 (Box 175, Folder 1278-1280)
- Correspondence, 3; 7.38 Cubic Feet
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1994 (Box 43, Folder 393)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1995, 1995 January-May (Box 43, Folder 394)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1995, 1995 June-December (Box 43, Folder 395)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1996, 1996 January-May (Box 43, Folder 396)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1996, 1996 June-December (Box 44, Folder 397)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1997, 1997 January-May (Box 44, Folder 398)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1997, 1997 June-December (Box 44, Folder 399)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1998, 1998 January-March (Box 44, Folder 400)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1998, 1998 April-June (Box 45, Folder 401)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1998, 1998 July-December (Box 45, Folder 402)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1999, 1999 January-August (Box 45, Folder 403)
  - Karen Davis Chronological File 1999, 1999 September-December (Box 45, Folder 404)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - A-B, 1994-2000 (Box 46, Folder 405)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - C, 1993-1999 (Box 46, Folder 406)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - D-F, 1993-1999 (Box 46, Folder 407)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - G-H, 1992-1999 (Box 47, Folder 408)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - I-L, 1994-1998 (Box 47, Folder 409)